coacht.com 2018-07-03

# Privacy Statement for coacht.com :: CoachT.com Tennessee High School Sports

**CoachT.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our website.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

This site contains links to other sites. **CoachT.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

We use Google and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company and we do not have access to this information.  
Google's use of the tracking cookies enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. For more information about Google's tracking cookie and to opt-out of the use of the cookie, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Other third-party companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

In addition, we have contracted with ValueClick to monitor certain pages of our website for the purpose of reporting website traffic, statistics, advertisement 'click-throughs', and/or other activities on our website. Where authorized by us, ValueClick may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to any party other than the Advertiser. For more information about how the information is collected and used by ValueClick, please see ValueClick's privacy policy at http://media.valueclick.com/privacy_consumer.shtml.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

### Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Only the owner of coacht.com, Jim Thompson, has access to any and all information on coacht.com's servers, and he will not allow anyone else to have access to this data.

### Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.  
This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

  1. You can send email to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#197a76787a716d597a76787a716d377a7674)

### Change/Modify

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.

  1. email [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#12717d73717a6652717d73717a663c717d7f)  

  2. online form [Edit User Info](http://tennessee.coacht.com/boards/index.php?act=UserCP&CODE=00)  

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact

Jim Thompson  
[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
